http://www.shimu.co.uk/pages/privacy

** COVID-19 update : Our showroom is now open again. Online and phone orders are also being processed as normal. **
Privacy Policy
Shimu is committed to respecting your privacy and to maintaining the trust and confidence of visitors to our website. We try to be as open as possible about how we treat your personal data when you use this site. You’ll find outlined below more information on how, when and why we collect your personal information, how we use it and details of any circumstances in which we may disclose it to others.
Website Cookies
Like most website, our site uses cookies to collect information.  This includes information about browsing and purchasing behaviour when you access the site, such as which pages you view, products you buy and your journey around our site.
You can find more detailed information about cookies, how we use them and what information they store under our Cookie Policy.
Google Analytics
When anyone visits www.shimu.co.uk we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. This is so that we can find out information such as the number of visitors to different parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.
Mailing list and email newsletters
As part of the registration process for our regular e-newsletters, we collect personal information. We use that information for a few reasons:
to let you know about things you’ve asked to be kept informed of (e.g. new products, sales);
to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information;
to check our records are right and to make sure that you’re happy with our products and service.
We don't rent or trade email lists with other organisations and businesses. We will never sell your data and we will keep your details safe and secure.
We will not e-mail you for marketing purposes unless you have given us your consent to do so or if we have a legitimate interest in doing so (for example, if we already have a relationship with you as a customer and we are letting you know about a similar product to one previously purchased). If we do e-mail you for this purpose, you will always have the opportunity to indicate whether you wish to ‘opt out’ of receiving similar information from Shimu in the future.
We use a third-party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our e-newsletter. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. For more information, please see MailChimp’s privacy notice. You can unsubscribe to our mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails or by emailing our customer service team at info@shimu.co.uk or by phoning us on 0800 0886800.
Ordering online
When you make a purchase through our website or fill out the enquiry form on our ‘contact us’ page, your personal details (your name, address, contact phone number and email address) will be recorded in our e-commerce system and entered into our database of contacts along with details of any purchase you make. We will use this information to fulfil your order or, if you need to contact us later on, so that we can provide a faster, more efficient service.
If you make a purchase we will also enter and store your personal details in our accounting package, Sage, in order to produce your invoice and receipt and to store details of previous purchases. We do not hold details of any credit or debit card information used to make purchases, other than the physical ‘merchant copy’ card receipts printed when a ‘card not present’ payment is made over the phone. These are stored securely.
Third Parties
We use a number specialist furniture delivery companies and couriers in order to carry out deliveries of our furniture and other items to customers’ homes. We will share only essential personal details (your name, address, contact numbers and email address) to allow these companies to contact you to arrange your delivery.
We do not share your personal details with any other company without your consent.
Access to your personal information
You are entitled to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold about you. If would like to obtain this information or request that we delete your details please email your request to our customer services team at info@shimu.co.uk.
Changes to this privacy notice
We review this privacy policy annually to ensure that it meets current regulations.
Enter your email address below to receive news and special offers by email
Contact Us
Mon-Fri 9:30am - 5:30pmSat 10:00am - 4:00pm(Showroom open Mon - Sat)info@shimu.co.ukcall: 0800 088 6800
© 2020 Shimu Ltd. All Rights Reserved. This site uses cookies.
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
Trustpilot
